xxxx.com.au 2005-06-15

# XXXX

> The purpose of this document is to tell you how Castlemaine Perkins Pty Limited (“XXXX ”, “we or “us”) manages your personal information.  We may vary the XXXX Privacy Policy from time to time.  We will notify you of any changes by publishing them on XXXX web sites.
> 
> XXXX is committed to the protection of your personal information. XXXX Privacy Policy tells you what sort of personal information we will typically hold, for what purpose and how we collect, hold, use, disclose and protect that personal information. 
> 
> Our Privacy Policy contains the following important information: 
> 
> Security of your information  
> Disclosure of your information  
> Collection of your personal information  
> How we use the personal information you give us  
> How we use information gathered from site usage  
> How & when you can Opt In to receive communication  
> How & when you can Opt Out of receiving communication  
> How to access, correct or update your information  
> What else you should know about Privacy  
> How to contact us
> 
> When you visit a XXXX web site, you are encouraged to read the information provided on the XXXX sites you are using each time you enter them. 
> 
> If you have any concerns, questions or complaints regarding privacy and management of your personal data by XXXX, please use the Contact Us button or email us at [consumerprivacy@xxxx.com.au](mailto:consumerprivacy@xxxx.com.au)
> 
> **_**__****__**Security of your information_**
> 
> We take all reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment accessed only by authorised persons for legitimate business purposes.  Data transmissions sent to or from XXXX are routinely monitored for quality control.  Unfortunately, as you may know, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information from misuse, loss and unauthorised access, we cannot guarantee the security of the passage of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. These activities are conducted at your own risk.  However, once we receive your data transmission, we take all reasonable steps to ensure its security. 
> 
> **_Secure destruction of your information_**
> 
> XXXX takes all reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is securely destroyed or de-identified when it is no longer needed for any purpose for which it was collected.
> 
> **_**_Disclosure of your information_**_**
> 
> The information we collect from you is held in accordance with all applicable privacy laws, industry codes and policies. XXXX will not reveal, disclose, sell, distribute, rent, licence, share or pass that information on to any third parties for marketing purposes.
> 
> However, XXXX may contract with third party organisations to administer and manage the data we collect from time to time. These organisations are required to keep all information confidential, or are subject to a statute or binding scheme, which imposes equivalent restrictions regarding the handling of personal information. 
> 
> Subject to the exceptions below, if we wish to use or disclose any of your personal information or data for any purpose other than those specified to you at the time of collection, we will not do so unless:
> 
> ·         we have notified you of the organisation(s) that will be receiving the data; and
> 
> ·         you have explicitly given us permission to do so by opting to receive third party offers when you registered on the site or at any subsequent point after registration. 
> 
> _**Exceptions to XXXX policy of non-disclosure**_
> 
> In certain circumstances we may disclose or use your personal information, for a purpose (“new purpose”) other than the primary purpose which is specified to you at the time of collection.
> 
> This will occur when:
> 
> ·  you would reasonably expect us to disclose the information for that   
>    new purpose; 
> 
> ·  the new purpose we plan to use your personal information for is   
>    related to the primary purpose that we initially disclosed to you on   
>    collection; and 
> 
> ·  it is impracticable for us to seek your consent.
> 
> In particular, XXXX reserves its rights to use or disclose your personal information:
> 
> ·  where there are reasonable grounds to believe that disclosure is   
>    necessary to prevent a serious and imminent threat to life or health;   
>    or
> 
> ·  where XXXX has reason to suspect that unlawful activity is or has   
>    been engaged in and uses or discloses your personal information or   
>    data to investigate that suspected unlawful activity; or 
> 
> ·  where the use or disclosure is authorised or required by law or   
>    where XXXX reasonably believes that it is reasonably necessary to   
>    enforce the law or prevent a criminal offence.
> 
>   
> **_**_Collection of your personal information_**  
> _**  
>  When XXXX collects your personal information via the Internet, competitions, surveys, promotional coupons and any other media we use to collect your personal information we will inform you of how the information will be used and disclosed. In all cases, your information will be held in accordance with all applicable privacy laws, industry codes and policies.
> 
> We will not collect sensitive information about you, which may reveal specific personal preferences or traits (including, for example, racial or ethnic origin, or your political views, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or details of health, disability or sexual activity or orientation) without your express consent.
> 
> The types of personal information that we generally collect from you will depend on the purpose for which you are providing your personal information. The information that we may collect will be gathered from what you choose to provide to us and, in the case of the Internet, from what we track through your use of our web sites.
> 
>   
> **_**_How we use the personal information you give us  
> _**  
> _**
> 
> We use your personal information for a number of reasons including:
> 
> **Date of Birth**
> 
> We need to ask for your date of birth to ensure that you are of legal drinking age. If you are not 18 years of age or over then you may not use a XXXX website. 
> 
> **Your contact details**
> 
> Contact information that we collect, such as name, e-mail address and phone number, is used for identification purposes and to allow us to contact you with personalised information on promotions and offers. You may opt out of receiving these communications by any or all of the contact methods you have provided at any time.  See the “How & when you can ‘Opt‑Out’ of receiving communication” section below for details.
> 
> **Gender**  
>  We may ask you to provide gender information to enable us to monitor the increasing involvement of women in the beer category and to tailor our marketing programs more effectively.
> 
> **Additional information about you and your interests**  
>  We may ask you to provide details of your drinking habits and preferred beer brands to enable us to understand our marketplace better and to tailor our marketing programs more effectively.
> 
> **Other information**  
>  From time to time we may also ask you to provide us with information on your wider interests either directly or through your participation in competitions, surveys, promotional coupons and the like. This information will be used to ensure that our marketing activities and communications are tailored to your needs and interests. We may also contact you with details of offers and activities, which we believe may be of interest to you based on the information you have provided to us. You will be given the option to opt out of receiving further communication in each instance.
> 
> **_**_How we use information gathered from site usage_**_**
> 
> **Your unique use of a XXXX web site**  
>  We may record information that we access automatically on your use of a XXXX web site, what areas of activity you participate in when you are there and where you have come into the site from. This usage information is used by us to monitor and improve the web site and our service to you.
> 
> **General XXXX web site usage**  
>  XXXX aggregates the data that is gathered from all individual users of XXXX web sites for analysis purposes (for example, we obtain information regarding web trends and web usage). Personally identifiable characteristics are removed and users remain anonymous, unless they have given prior specific consent for XXXX to recognise their usage.
> 
> This information may be shared with third parties for the purpose of examining general web and Internet trends and demographics and for measuring the site’s performance.
> 
> We may use or disclose this personal information or data for a purpose other than the primary purpose (specified above) if you would reasonably expect us to use the personal information for that other purpose, the other purpose is related to the primary purpose and it is impracticable for us to seek your consent. 
> 
> **_**_How & when you can 'Opt In' to receive communication_**_**
> 
> XXXX will provide you an express opportunity to make a request to receive further marketing communications from XXXX, via an "opt-in" mechanism. You may opt in when you register on a XXXX website.
> 
> You may opt in at anytime after that by contacting XXXX by email via the Contact Us link on a XXXX website and notifying us that you wish to receive further communications from XXXX.
> 
> **_**_How & when you can 'Opt Out' of receiving communication_**_**
> 
> You will not receive marketing communications from XXXX unless you have expressly “opted in” to receive them.
> 
> We will provide you an XXXX, via an "opt-out" mechanism. You may opt out at any time after you have Opted In  by using the following options:
> 
> ·  clicking on the Opt Out box, which will be included in any   
>    communication which you receive from XXXX; or 
> 
> ·  contacting XXXX by email via the Contact Us link on a XXXX website   
>    and notifying us that you do not wish to receive further  
>    communications  from XXXX. 
> 
> **_**_How to access, correct or update your information_**_**
> 
> You may request access to and correction of all personal information which XXXX holds about you at any time, by sending an email via the Contact Us button on the XXXX website or emailing us at consumerprivacy@xxxx.com.au.  Your request will be processed in a reasonable time.  There is no fee for requesting access to your information, however you may be charged the reasonable cost of processing your request.
> 
>   
> XXXX reserves the right to decline to correct or update personal information about you where:
> 
> ·  providing access would be unlawful, would be likely to prejudice an    
>    investigation of possible unlawful activity, would be likely to    
>    prejudice law enforcement activities, or denying access is   
>    specifically authorised by law; or 
> 
> ·  your request for access is frivolous or vexatious; or
> 
> ·  providing access would have an unreasonable impact upon the    
>    privacy of other individuals; or
> 
> ·  providing access would reveal the intentions of XXXX in relation to    
>    negotiations with you in such a way as to prejudice those   
>    negotiations; or
> 
> ·  providing access would reveal evaluative information generated   
>    within XXXX in connection with a commercially sensitive decision   
>    making process.
> 
> If XXXX declines you access to your personal information or refuses to correct your personal information, we will provide you with the reasons for our decision.  
> 
> 
> **_**_What else you should know about privacy_**_** Remember that you will have to exercise reasonable care when accessing, or providing information, where you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer. For further Privacy information, please refer to The Australian Privacy Commissioner’s Web Site by linking to [http://www.privacy.gov.au/](http://www.privacy.gov.au/).
> 
> **_**_How to contact us_**_**
> 
> If you have any concerns, questions or complaints regarding privacy and management of your personal data, please contact XXXX by using the Contact Us button on the website or by emailing us at [consumerprivacy@xxxx.com.au](mailto:consumerprivacy@xxxx.com.au)
> 
> Thank you for taking the time to read the XXXX Privacy Policy.
